Guide to the Central Washington University Library Department, Annual Reports of the Librarian 1921-1961, 1963-1988
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
Central Washington University Library Department, Annual Reports of the Librarian
1921-1961, 1963-1988
Central Washington University, Archives and Special Collections 400 E University Way Ellensburg, WA 98926 (509) 963-1717 http://www.lib.cwu.edu/Archives-Special-Collections archive@cwu.edu
RG011-04-12
Central Washington University Library
1.5 cubic feet 3 letter sized document boxes Printed annual reports. Older reports have brittle edges and discoloration; newer volumes are in good condition.
This collection contains annual reports of all library departments at Central Washington University, 1921-1988.
Historical Note
The Central Washington University library began in Barge Hall, moved into Bouillon Hall in 1962, and finally to a new building in 1973. In 2003, the building was named in honor of Dr. James E. Brooks, former president of Central Washington University.
Along with Central Washington University library reports, this collection includes reports from Ellensburg's Elementary School library for appropriate years. Reports present data on expenditures, staffing, and other operational information.
Central Washington University began as the Washington State Normal School in 1891. In 1937, the school was rechristened the Central Washington College of Education. In 1961, the school became Central Washington State College and, finally, in 1977, Central Washington University.
Arranged chronologically.
Open to the public for educational research.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Central Washington University. Library
Ellensburg (Wash.)
Central Washington University--History; Library statistics--United States
Washington (State); Colleges and Universities
- Annual reports, 1921-1929 (Box-folder 1-1)
- Annual reports, 1931-1932 (Box-folder 1-2)
- Annual reports, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 1-3)
- Annual reports, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 1-4)
- Annual reports, 1934-1935 (Box-folder 1-5)
- Annual reports, 1935-1936 (Box-folder 1-6)
- Annual reports, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 1-7)
- Annual reports, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 1-8)
- Annual reports, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 1-9)
- Annual reports, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 1-10)
- Annual reports, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 1-11)
- Annual reports, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 1-12)
- Annual reports, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 1-13)
- Annual reports, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 1-14)
- Annual reports, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 1-15)
- Annual reports, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 1-16)
- Annual reports, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 1-17)
- Annual reports, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 1-18)
- Annual reports, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 1-19)
- Annual reports, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 1-20)
- Annual reports, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 1-21)
- Annual reports, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 1-22)
- Annual reports, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 2-1)
- Annual reports, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 2-2)
- Annual reports, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 2-3)
- Annual reports, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 2-4)
- Annual reports, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 2-5)
- Annual reports, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 2-6)
- Annual reports, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 2-7)
- Annual reports, 1961 (Box-folder 2-8)
- Annual reports, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 2-9)
- Annual reports, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 2-10)
- Annual reports, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 2-11)
- Annual reports, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 2-12)
- Annual reports, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 2-13)
- Annual reports, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 2-14)
- Annual reports, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 2-15)
- Annual reports, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 3-1)
- Annual reports, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 3-2)
- Annual reports, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 3-3)
- Annual reports, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 3-4)
- Annual reports, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 3-5)
- Annual reports, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 3-6)
- Annual reports, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 3-7)
- Annual reports, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 3-8)
- Annual reports, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3-9)
- Annual reports, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 3-10)
- Annual reports, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 3-11)
- Annual reports, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 3-12)
- Annual reports, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 3-13)
- Annual reports, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 3-14)
- Annual reports, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 3-15)
- Annual reports, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 3-16)
- Annual reports, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 3-17)
- Annual reports, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 3-18)